If there is a welcome to another session, the successfully escalated the privileges from
user to admin admin to system, we have seen various methods to how to do that.
So in this section, we are going to discuss about the persistence, so this one of important
things for all the threat actors and their teammates. So if you can able to take your malicious
executable inside the environment, any of the machine, so let's see, you have a malware,
you successfully did an initial access and you just executed the malware in one of the
machines inside the organization. But there is a problem if they restart or the machine
or if they shut down the machine and again they start there. So at that time, we were
malware will be get terminated, right? So there will be no connection from your side
if they restarted the machine because that executable has been literally Terminator by
the operating system. So there is a way to achieve the goal for if they restarted the
machine or if they shut down the machine and if they again start there, you were executed
or it will be automatically executed without any manual thing, it will be an automation
thing. So windows have set of persistent mechanism, so this is one of interview questions,
so the blue teamers as well as their teamers, there are five kind of persistence in the
windows machine, in Linux machine there was like cron jobs, services and startup, but will
be focusing on windows, so windows have five kind of persistence, so the owners registry
and the two is start of folder, the three could be a WMI, we will be seeing windows management
instrumentation and four will be scheduled task and five will be a services, okay?
So in this section, we are going to fulfill the persistent later activities, so we will
be seeing how the threat actors will be achieving the persistence inside the machine, okay?
So the commands will be seen here, I will be giving that in our resource session, don't
worry, the all the commands which I have mentioned, it will be executed in the active
incidents, which we have handled by the threat actors, okay? So whenever they're targeting,
whenever they're attacking any organization, we'll be occurring, this kind of persistence
based commands from the machine, okay? So I hope you have a bit understanding about
what is a persistence, so I'll be going for one more time, so what if if they restart
the machine, your executable will be get terminated and it will be not getting any connection
from that, so you'll be taking your executable in a persistence mode, like if they restart
the machine or if they shut down the machine and take up again, so that malware will
be get automatically executed by the Windows operating system and you'll be getting
connection on the post came back online, okay? So you don't need to do any, any sort
of things, everything will be handled by the Windows operating system, okay? Let me, let
me create some malware using the MS of venom, I think this coming in sudden cover in this
post, if I not cover, so I'll be explaining this command, so here you need to give which
payloads you will be choosing, so I'll be choosing the Windows based payloads and
the metadata and reverse TCP, this is the pair of which I am choosing and L host will
be my calling machine post, that will be a I have a config and it's the IP was on 18.27,
let me 92.168.18.27 and L port will be the port, you can choose any port, I'll be choosing
like 87.69 and that's your feel be the format, which format you need, I'll be keeping
this in a EXE format, EXE equitable format, and I'll be saving my malware as a process
to mal.exe, okay? P-E-R-S-A-S-T mal.exe, so once I execute this, so this method is like
you are creating a new malware, okay, let me do L-S, so here you can find our malware which
has been created, so let me do one more thing, I'll be creating, I'll be listening, I'll
be starting a listener using the MS of console, okay? So let me do that, so let me do
that. So I'll be choosing the listener exploit multi handler, so it will handle multiple
connections, and I'll be setting the pair or a, a, the pair would be generator, a, meter,
and L-Port, on 92.168.18.27 and L-Port will be the port, which we have given when we create
a dirty malware, 897, I feel that support which I have opened, which I got again, 8769, yeah. So now,
everything, I feel everything has been settled, so let me deliver this malware, to my, let
me deliver this malware to my Windows machine, C-P-E-P-O-S-S-S, I'll put it in a, I'll
put it in a Apache folder, and let me start Apache, so I'm going to the Windows machine,
and I will be uploading this, okay, done, yeah, we just created a malware, as well as we
have created a listener for our reverse connection, and in the next video, we'll be adding
this power system, ALD, or T-X-E inside the rent key registry, I have already mentioned,
there are five kind of power systems we can do, so in the next video, we are going to add
this registry keys, okay, so let's hop off from here, and we'll continue our discussion
next video, you guys, bye bye.